907 Forest Drive, Garner, NC 27529 (919) 921-7562 massengillashley@icloud.com ashleymassengill.github.io

ashlevmassengill.com

OVERVIEW

Through my experiences, I have learned where my strengths lie. I enjoy writing code and turning designs into interactive products through HTML and CSS. My goal is to continue growing my experience and knowledge in ways that allow me to tap into the creative and organized sides of my personality to create a product that is the best outcome for everyone.

STRENGTHS

★ Creative Thinking

★ Great Eye for Detail

★ Analytical Thinking

★ Extreme Efficiency

★ Teaching Skills

★ Organization

PROJECT HISTORY

Front-End Developer, Anthracite Theme

[i] Jun 2018

Anthracite is the enterprise level theme template of Sprowt, a Drupal7 based sitebuild product developed by Coalmarch Productions.

• Drupal build • Theme styling • Template maintnance & enhancement Tech: Drupal7, Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, jQuery, SourceTree

Front-End Developer, Teambuilder (Forgely Hire)

🗓 Jun 2017

A careers mini-site for Coalmarch clients built on Drupal7 with a paragraphs based structure to aid in employment recruitment.

 Drupal build
Product styling
Product maintnance
enhancement Tech: Drupal7, Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, jQuery, SourceTree

UI Designer & Developer, diaBEATthis

🗓 Jan 2017

diaBEATthis is a website and web app focused on assisting diabetes suferers track and manage the various aspects of their disease.

• Visual Design • Style Guide • Branding • Page Layouts • Front End Code Tech: Illustrator, Photoshop, Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, Skeleton, iQuery, Github

WORK HISTORY

- Built and styled custom designed client sites on Drupal7 platform.
- Developed proprietary features and templates for Drupal7 based Sprowt website platform.
- Lead front-end developer and product owner on Teambuilder, Coalmarch.com.
- Team organization lead including documentation, Pantheon maintenance.

Database Manager, RCI, Inc.

i Apr 2016 - Jul 2016

(\$) Raleigh, NC

- Managed internal tech support including computer hardware, software, phone systems, servers, and website.
- Guided implementation of new AMS through search, demon, contract, setup and testing phases into training and go-live.
- Created and maintained all reporting operations for each department.

Meetings Specialist, RCI, Inc.

i Dec 2010 - Apr 2016

Raleigh, NC

- Produced event based website layouts and coding.
- Managed all event registrations for 10+ attendee events to 1500+ attedee events.
- Created all meeting collateral for international events from general education to conventions and trade shows.

TECHNOLOGIES

CSS3 SASS HTMI 5 Drupal7 Skeleton Bootstrap GitHub iQuery iTerm Mac OS Adobe Illustrator Jira Adobe Photoshop Adobe InDesign Atom

Adobe Acrobat Microsoft Office Trello

Apple iWork

Google Docs

Crystal Reports

EDUCATION

UI Design, The Iron Yard

i Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

(\$) Raleigh, NC

East Carolina University

i Aug 2001 - May 2003 (\$) Greenville, NC

VOLUNTEER HISTORY

Guest Services NC State Athletics

🗓 Aug 2016 - current

(\$) Raleigh, NC

Box Office & Boutique Assistant Carolina Ballet

🗓 Aug 2010 - current

Raleigh, NC

Admissions & Ticketing Services USGA Men's & Women's US Open

[i] Jul 2014

(\$) Pinehurst, NC

AFFILIATIONS

- Women Who Code Raleigh/Durham
- AIGA Raleigh
- Triangle UXPA

INTERESTS













